pactera.com 2017-05-15

# Privacy | Pactera

**ONLINE PRIVACY STATEMENT**

Updated Date: April 29, 2016

Pactera Technology International Ltd. (Pactera), is dedicated to protecting the confidentiality and privacy of information entrusted to it. As part of this fundamental obligation, Pactera is committed to the appropriate protection and use of personal information (sometimes referred to as "personally identifiable information" or "PII") that has been collected online.

Please review this Privacy Statement ("Privacy Statement") to learn more about how we collect, use, share and protect the PII that we have obtained.

Generally, our intent is to collect only the personal information that is provided voluntarily by online visitors so that we can offer information and/or services to those individuals or offer information about employment opportunities.

**_Collection of Information_**

This website collects various types of information, such as:

·  Voluntarily provided information which may include your name, address, email address, billing and/or credit card information etc., which may be used when you purchase products and/or services and to deliver the services you have requested.

·  Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs.    

Please rest assured that this site shall only collect personal information that you knowingly and willingly provide by way of surveys, completed contact forms, and emails. It is the intent of this site to use personal information only for the purpose for which it was requested and any additional uses specifically provided on this site.

We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.

**_Use of Information Collected_**

Pactera may collect and may make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website and to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At times, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services that may be available to you from pactera.com. Pactera may also be in contact with you with regards to completing surveys and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.

Pactera does not now, nor will it in the future, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.

Pactera may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that our users may frequent in an effort to gleam what types of services and/or products may be the most popular to customers or the general public.

Pactera may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:

·  Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Pactera and/or our website;

·  Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Pactera; and

·  Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of www.pactera.com and/or the general public.

**_Children Under Age of 13_**

Pactera does not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13) without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected on anyone under the age of thirteen (13), we shall immediately take the necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system's database. Anyone under the age of thirteen (13) must seek and obtain parent or guardian permission to use this website.

**_Unsubscribe or Opt-Out_**

All users and/or visitors to our website have the option to discontinue receiving communication from us and/or reserve the right to discontinue receiving communications by way of email or newsletters. To discontinue or unsubscribe to our website please send an email that you wish to unsubscribe to info@pactera.com. If you wish to unsubscribe or opt-out from any third party websites, you must go to that specific website to unsubscribe and/or opt-out.

**_Links to Other Web Sites_**

Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. Pactera does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Statement applies only and solely to the information collected by our website.

**_Security_**

Pactera shall endeavor and shall take precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, and destruction of the user's personal information under our control. Despite Pactera’s efforts, however, security cannot be guaranteed against all threats. Those individuals who have access to the data are required to maintain the confidentiality of such information. 

**_Changes to Privacy Statement_**

Pactera may modify this Privacy Statement from time to time to reflect our current privacy practices. When we make changes to this statement, we will revise the “updated” date at the top of this page. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Statement to be informed about how Pactera is protecting your information.

**_Acceptance of Terms_**

Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Statement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, then you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.

**_Policy Questions_**

Pactera is committed to protecting the online privacy of your personal information. If you have questions or comments about our administration of your personally identifiable information, please contact us at [info@pactera.com](mailto:info@pactera.com).
